Soldier. Mother. So many expectations.
Fort Bliss is a war, drama film directed by Claudia Myers.
After returning home from an extended tour in Afghanistan, a decorated U.S.
Army medic and single mother struggles to rebuild
her relationship with her young son.
Maggie Swann, played by Michelle Monaghan.
Alma, played by Emmanuelle Chriqui.
Staff Sergeant Donovan, played by Pablo Schreiber.
Richard, played by Ron Livingston.
Garver, played by Freddy Rodríguez.
Staff Sergeant Malcolm, played by Dash Mihok.
Fort Bliss is a 2014 American drama film directed and written by
Claudia Myers, a military-based drama set on Fort Bliss.
The film stars Michelle Monaghan, Ron Livingston, Pablo
Schreiber, Emmanuelle Chriqui, and Dash Mihok.
The film explores themes of war veteran, woman director, afghanistan veteran.
The tone is emotional.